Instantly see your friends list, party invites,
messages, and achievements in the guide.
From Home, move left to open the guide.
See who’s online and who’s in a party,
and join up or send your own invite.
Below Friends is Parties, where you can manage
your current party or invite friends to a new one.
Down one more is Achievements. While you’re playing
a game, double-tap the Xbox button to open the guide.
Move down to Achievements to see your progress
and what you need to do for more Gamerscore.
Next is Messages. Read recently received messages,
or send messages using text or a voice recording.
Check Notifications for the things you may have missed, like
party invites, new friend requests, and recent achievements.
Below that, you can get to all the Settings for your Xbox One.
Kinect mic and power settings are right in the guide,
and for everything else, choose All settings.
And last on the guide is Snap, where you can launch snappable apps.
When you’re done, press B to close the guide
and get back to your game.
Discover more! Get information and tips from Xbox Help.